Υπάρχουν και διαφορετικά είδη γάλακτος;
Σωστά. Αν και βασικά όλα είναι ίδια, υπάρχουν διαφορετικά είδη ανάλογα με το πως είναι προετοιμασμένα.
Διαφορετικά είδη;
Yes, just like in tea.
Depending on which leaves are picked and how they're prepared, the same leaves can be very different.
People, too?
Χμμ;
Υπάρχουν και διαφορετικά είδη ανθρώπων;
Χμμ, λοιπόν, αντί για είδη, κάθε άτομο είναι διαφορετικό με το δικό του τρόπο.
Για παράδειγμα, δε σου αρέσει το τσάι, αλλά υπάρχουν και άνθρωποι σαν κι εμένα που το λατρεύουν.
There are also people whose stomach gets upset when they drink milk, but there also those who don't have that happen to them, right?
However, there also people who learn to drink it when they grow up.
Lain, you’ll probably learn to drink tea, you know.
Δεν είναι ούτε καλό, ούτε κακό.
Είναι φυσιολογικό το ότι υπάρχουν διαφορετικοί τύποι ανθρώπων.
That's why you can be proud of what makes you unique!
Να είμαι περήφανη γι' αυτό;
I’m sorry... That’s right, you worry, don’t you?
You don’t have to boast about it, but there’s no need to mind what other people think, is what I meant to say.
I have weird dreams. Is that different, too?
You may think it's different, but in fact that’s normal.
Αν ανησυχείς γι' αυτό, μπορώ να βοηθήσω.
Όχι στο να σταματήσεις να βλέπεις εκείνα τα όνειρα, αλλά να σε βοηθήσω πως να εξηγήσεις πράγματα που δεν καταλαβαίνεις.
Αν έρθεις σ' εμένα με τα προβλήματά σου, θα είμαι πολύ χαρούμενη.
You know, I’ve studied a lot to help you answer those kinds of questions; I’m still studying, actually.
If you’re ever in trouble or something, I'd be glad if you could come and talk with me.
I’d like to know more about you, Lain.
Θα ήταν εντάξει;
Χαίρομαι!
Starting today, you and I are friends!
Please come and play sometime!
Το υπόσχεσαι;
Θα ήθελα να σε ρωτήσω και για μερικά πράγματα!
Μπορείς να με ρωτήσεις ό, τι θέλεις.
If I don’t know the answer, I’ll look up the answer for you.
Θα σου ετοιμάσω και το αγαπημένο σου ρόφημα.
Τι είναι αυτό;
Γάλα που δε σου ταράζει το στομάχι!